const qa = [
    { "question": "A species that is so important that an ecosystem could collapse without it is called a", "answers": ["Keystone species", "Apex species", "Endemic species"], "correct": 1 },
    { "question": "The circulation of carbon through the Earth's ecosystems is called the", "answers": ["Hydrological cycle", "Sulfur cycle", "Carbon cycle"], "correct": 3 },
    { "question": "Foreign plants that take up space meant for native plants are referred to as ", "answers": ["Terminator", "Invasive", "Primary proceducers"], "correct": 2 },
    { "question": "The variety of life present in an ecosystem is known as", "answers": ["Biofuel", "Biodiversity", "Biosurgence"], "correct": 2 },
    { "question": "When an organism benefits from looking like something in its environment this is called", "answers": ["Benthos", "Symbiosis", "Mimicry"], "correct": 3 },
    { "question": "Animals that gets most of their nutrition from fruit are called", "answers": ["Nectarivores", "Herbivores", "Frugivores"], "correct": 3 },
    { "question": "When the pH of the ocean decreases it is called", "answers": ["Alkalization", "Bioaccumulation", "Acidification"], "correct": 3 },
    { "question": "A terrestrial ecosystem is one that is located", "answers": ["On water", "On land", "In the upper atmosphere"], "correct": 2 },
    { "question": "When 2 species interact in a way that is good for both of them is called", "answers": ["Commensalism", "Parasitism", "Mutualism"], "correct": 3 },
    { "question": "Each year birds travel long distance to get warm, then return when the weather changes is called", "answers": ["Migration", "Hibernation", "Estivation"], "correct": 1 },
    { "question": "What would you call a dog that has fleas living on it", "answers": ["A vector", "A host", "A parasite"], "correct": 2 },
    { "question": "An ecosystem is made up of biotic factors and", "answers": ["Abiotic factors", "Unbiotic factors", "Exobiotic factors"], "correct": 1 },
    { "question": "If a species is said to be 'arboreal', where does it live?", "answers": ["Underground", "In trees", "In caves"], "correct": 2 },
    { "question": "The natural environment in which any organism lives is called its", "answers": ["Habitat", "Burrow", "Biome"], "correct": 1 },
    { "question": "The world ecology is Greek for the study of ", "answers": ["Environment", "Living relations", "Water"], "correct": 2 }
]